Let's welcome Bobby Jameson Travis,
defensive lineman from Auburn, your
186th pick of the sixth round in this
draft. BJT, can I call you BJT? I feel
like I know you already from the two
minutes we've been on this Zoom call.
>> Yeah, you call BJT.
>> My man, I bet you ready. I bet you're
ready to take a bite out of the big
apple, man. So, come on. Talk to me.
What was it like when you saw that 2011
number pop up on your phone? Actually, I
I was just sitting down um really just
being patient and waiting my turn and I
seen NY Giants. Uh it popped up. I'm
like, "Oh, snap." I'm like I'm like,
"I'mma ask that." Then I got that call.
I was very excited.
>> All right, man. Let's talk a little bit
of football here, man. You got drafted
be an anchor on this defensive line. I'm
sitting here looking at it. You anchor
the Auburn defensive line that ranked
top 10 in rushing yards allowed. That's
been something that the Giants have
struggled at in recent years. Talk to
me. How you going to come in? You going
to help fill that void and uh and stop
the run with the de with the linebackers
you have behind you now?
>> Oh yeah. Um shoot really twoon-one
somebody free. And that's like always my
mindset. I get double team in the
trenches. Uh I know a linebacker gonna
come in the field. So I'm do everything
that's possible to stop the run. Um
really because I consider myself as a
run stop.
>> Okay.
>> And I and I
pride.
>> Was that what a lot of the conversations
were like with you and the Giants, you
know, throughout the course of this
draft process? Kind of take us in those
rooms and those those Zoom calls and
those those conversations.
>> It was like like me me and the Giants
like
we we locked in for sure. like I had a
great time on my 30 visit there and like
I connected with everybody in the rooms
in every room actually
>> uh with all the meetings we had. So I
had a great connection with them.
>> Um and it really just a blessing to um
for them to draft me. I'm ready to go to
work.
>> Last but not least, I like to ask the
players, what's your why? When we
talking about the dog days, things
aren't going right. What's your why?
What's that that that that reason or
reasons that you wake up, you show up to
work, and you go 100% no matter what?
>> Uh my why is really my mom and my
children. Uh my mom, she raised she had
a lot of she had seven kids and adopted
seven kids of her own. And really, she
she's my single parent mama. Um my dad
passed away in 2013 from natural cause.
So, she really took in that dad and mom
role and she stood strong and uh really
made a way for us. And then my kids, you
know, they more supportive than
anything. Uh they was at all my games
and all that ever since they was born.
So really, that's my mom and my kids.
>> What's one thing in New York City you're
excited to do or to experience for the
first time?
>> Man, I ain't trying to experience
nothing. I'm ready to get to work.
>> That's what I'm ready to get to work.
[laughter]
Well, we can't wait to get you in the
building, man. That was a great answer
right there. Can't wait to get you in
the building. Congratulations and uh we
we'll see you in a little bit, bro.
>> Yes, sir.
[music]